hey what's up guys this is gee here with kevin trainings
嘿，伙计们，我是凯文
welcome to this quick video in which i'm going to respond to
欢迎观看我的短视频，这个视频要回答一些问题
a question that i receive here a lot on
一些我在KBTrainings收到的问题
kb trainings
as you know cable trainers i go from zero to engineer so most of you or some of you
KBTrainning是一个从0到成为工程师的系列
are beginners in this industry in
你们中大多数人是网络行业的初学者
networking in general
应该是吧
and you're asking yourself what are the
你们想知道
best books that you can read
你应该读什么书
as a beginner in networking what books can you read
作为网络初学者，您可以阅读哪些书籍
to get you to master all the concept of networking
让你掌握网络的所有概念
as you know here on kb trainings i share with you most of what i know and what i'm still learning in this field
正如您在 kb 培训中所知道的那样，我与您分享了我所知道的大部分内容以及我在该领域仍在学习的内容
so i'm a network professional
所以我是网络专业的
but if you've been on this channel for a while
但是如果你已经在这个频道上呆了一段时间
you might have seen my video in which i talk about books
你可能看过我谈论书籍的视频
i talk about reading what i think in general is that
关于阅读我认为
you should read of course
你当然应该阅读
but i'm not a book guy
但我不是书友
you know that book person who has a huge library behind him with all kind of books
你知道那个书人，他身后有一个巨大的图书馆，里面有各种各样的书
it's kind of disappearing this is 2020
但那已经不常见了， 2020 年了
we have the internet we have a lot of things so i think
我们有互联网我们有很多东西所以我想
if you really want to read you don't need to invest into a lot of books
如果你真的想阅读你不需要投资很多书
you should invest into something that
你应该学会利用互联网
will make you know what you have to research on the internet
这里有所有你需要的东西
and you can pretty much read anything on google on many websites
你几乎可以在许多网站上的谷歌上阅读任何内容
and by the way on kb trainings i just started a blog
顺便说一下kb培训我刚开始写博客
so i'm going to be uh writing articles in this blog here
所以我会在这个博客上写文章
if you go on the website and
如果您访问网站并且
you click blog um this is the first article like
你点击博客嗯这是第一篇文章
most of the videos like every i mean not every
大多数视频都像每个我的意思不是每个
but most of the videos on this channel will be an article
但是这个频道上的大部分视频都是一篇文章
this is the exact article in which i'm responding to this specific question about
这是我正在回答这个具体问题的确切文章
the books that you can read i'm not saying that don't buy books
你能读的书我不是说不买书
but you have the internet that's where you can read a lot
但是您拥有可以阅读很多内容的互联网
you can read most of the things on the internet
您可以阅读互联网上的大部分内容
but if you have to buy a book or if you want to study
但是如果你必须买一本书或者你想学习
if you are a beginner
如果你是初学者
i'm going to advise you to get certified
我会建议你获得认证
you need to pick a certification a networking certification
你需要选择一个认证 一个网络认证
and study for the cert and get the book for that specific certification
并学习证书并获得该特定证书的书
and at the end of the cert you have the knowledge
并且在证书结束时你有知识
and your knowledge will be structured in your head
你的知识将在你的脑海中形成
because if you are studying without any kind of plan or any kind of blueprint
因为如果你在没有任何计划或蓝图的情况下学习
you're uh going to be all over the place
你会很迷茫
there's a lot to learn in networking
因为网络有很多东西能学
so if you have a certification it's going to be much easier for you
因此，如果您有认证，那对您来说会容易得多
so the two certifications that i'm recommending
所以我推荐的两个认证
first the comptia network plus
首先是comptia network plus
it's a very good one it's vendor neutral
这是一个非常好的供应商中立的
it's good to get when you are getting your feet in the industry
当您涉足该行业时，这是一件好事
i started with it and then i went to the ccna
我从它开始，然后我去了 ccna
and the second one you might have guessed is the ccna
你可能已经猜到的第二个是 ccna
so if you are studying for the network plus it will teach you a lot of concept of networking
所以如果你正在为网络学习加上它会教你很多网络的概念
and it's all going to be structured
所有的概念都能建立起来
for those two certifications if you want to get the books for network plus
如果您想获得用于网络的书籍，请获得这两个认证
let's go on amazon
让我们来到亚马逊
if you do um network plus on amazon you get some books
如果你在亚马逊上做 um network plus 你会得到一些书
and i can recommend any of these books
我可以推荐任何这些书
this one for example um
这个例如嗯
or this other one but i i'll give you a link um to to get a book for on network plus
或者这个另一个，但我会给你一个链接，你可以在网络上买一本书加
and if you're looking for the ccna you can just um type ccna 200 301
如果您正在寻找 ccna，您可以输入 ccna 200 301
and this is what you're going to get
这就是你要得到的
yeah this is the the one that i prefer
是的，这是我更喜欢的那个
and if you get this one you're going to study for your cert
如果你得到这个，你将学习你的证书
and you will get certified after a few months of studies
经过几个月的学习，您将获得认证
and you also need to check out of course the official pages of these certifications
当然，您还需要查看这些认证的官方页面
if you go on compia.com i mean comptia.org
如果您访问 compia.com，我的意思是 comptia.org
you can see this is the official page for the network plus
你可以看到这是网络加的官方页面
it gives you the details about the exam
它为您提供有关考试的详细信息
and if you fill out this form
如果你填写这张表格
and you submit it's going to send you
你提交它会发送给你
the exam objectives
考试目标
and some practice questions for you to know exactly what it is
和一些练习题让你确切地知道它是什么
so personally i prefer the ccna because it's more practical practical
我个人更喜欢ccna，因为它更实用
the network plus is vendor neutral so sometimes it's kind of hard to master some concept
network+是供应商中立的，所以有时很难掌握一些概念
because you don't have any vendor that you can practice on
因为你没有可以练习的供应商
but if you go with the ccna this is the blueprint for the ccna
但如果你选择 ccna，这就是 ccna 的蓝图
if you just type ccna 300 um 201 i mean 200 301 blueprint
如果您只输入 ccna 300 um 201 我的意思是 200 301 蓝图
this is what you get uh it's right here
这就是你得到的，它就在这里
it's a pdf you have a list of topics or concepts that you have to know
这是一个 pdf，你有一个你必须知道的主题或概念的列表
before going and taking the exam
在去参加考试之前
this is going to help you
这会帮助你
this is going to uh just structure whatever you have to know
这将只是构建你必须知道的任何东西
i also recommend to get some kind of training videos
我还建议获取某种培训视频
i do videos myself on cabbagetrends.com if you are interested
如果您有兴趣，我会在 cabbagetrends.com 上自己制作视频
but any um any trainer or any training company is able to train you
但是任何嗯任何培训师或任何培训公司都可以培训你
and walk you through the exam blueprint
并引导您完成考试蓝图
until you master everything and you can go and take the exam
直到你掌握了一切，你可以去参加考试
so that's uh that's what i can tell you
所以这就是我可以告诉你的
but again remember you have the biggest book in the world
但再次记住你有世界上最大的书
you have the internet
你有互联网
you should know how to search the internet
你应该知道如何搜索互联网
you have youtube
你有 youtube
you should go on youtube and watch people that are doing networking stuff
你应该在 youtube 上观看那些正在做网络工作的人
you yeah you have all those means of study
你你拥有所有这些学习方法
so today you can just be alone and be in your bedroom
所以今天你可以一个人呆在卧室里
but still get a lot of knowledge
但还是能学到很多知识
because a lot of people are online just like me uh saying
因为很多人都在线就像我说的那样
i'm showing you what we do and showing you what is really necessary
向您展示我们所做的 向您展示真正需要的东西
in this world right now as a professional
在这个世界上，现在作为一名专业人士
so yeah that's it that's all i can tell you and
所这就是我能告诉你的全部
i'll be doing a lot of ask me anything type of video
我会做很多问我任何类型的视频
so if you like this don't forget to leave the comment and like the video
所以如果你喜欢这个不要忘记留下评论并喜欢视频
subscribe if you if you are a tech guy and you like more of this
如果您是技术人员并且喜欢更多内容，请订阅
i will be coming with a lot of videos on the channel
我将在频道上发布很多视频
so don't forget to do that for me and check out the blog
所以不要忘记为我做这件事并查看博客
and if you have any comment
如果你有任何意见
just put it down below and i'll be able to follow that
只要把它放在下面，我就可以查看
other than that thank you for watching and i'll see you in the next video bye
除此之外，谢谢你的收看，我会在下一个视频中见到你，再见